# **Emily Mehegan**

Through my five years of work in the hospitality industry I have gained experience in the many roles that are required in restuarants and cafés. These include waitressing, working in kitchen and as a barista. I have also had retail experience selling coffee beans and appliences at 'Cottle on Coventry'.

# **Experience**

O 2021 - Current

Brickhead Collectables | Newcomb, Geelong

### Admin Assistant | Sales

- Completing stock take on a wide range of products and inputing them into an online system/Microsoft Excel
- Completing online orders for customers in a timly matter to ensure packages are sent out on time
- Working independently meeting weekly/daily tasks
- Working at multiple conventions a year (e.g Comic Con, PAX) completing sales and providing information on products to customers
- Creating new online listings for incoming products/updating website with current products

2021 - Current

The Coffee Stop | Newcomb, Geelong

### Barista | Waitress | Cook

- Making coffees and looking after upkeep of machine and appliences
- Working in a kitchen cooking a range of items and plating dishes
- Keeping on top of café stock. This includes ordering and packing away stock to ensure café is running smoothly
- Aiding in the training of new staff
- Experience in both opening and closing of the café. This also includes till balencing at the end of the day

**Q** 2017 - 2021

Cottle on Coventry I South Melbourne, Melbourne

#### **Waitress**

- Selling coffee beans and coffee appliences to customers, providing information on different coffee makers and coffee beans
- Memorising different coffee tasting notes to provide customers with adequate information before purchase
- Welcoming and seating customers in a friendly manner
- Aiding customers on menu choices while taking orders and looking after multiple tables at a time

### Contact

#### **Phone**

0432 566 208

#### **Email**

emimehegan@gmail.com

#### **Address**

1100 Barrabool Rd Barrabool

VIC 3221

### **Education**

2006 - 2010

**Ceres Primary School, Ceres** 

2011 - 2018

**Christian College, Highton** 

2019-2022

**Deakin University, Waurn Ponds** 

Bachelor of International Studies Major: Anthropology

# **Expertise**

- Barista
- Administration
- Waitressing
- Customer Service
- Cooking
- Sales

# Language

**English** 

### Reference

**Tim Johnson** 

Owner, The Coffee Stop

Phone: 0458 023 386

**Bec Smallwood** 

Manager, Brickhead Collectable

**Phone:** 0423 089 601